prx.org 2019-06-14

# PRX – PRX Privacy Policy

Your use of the PRX Web site constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and consent to the terms herein. Please see “Information We Collect and How We Use It” to learn more about our collection and use of user information.

###  **Introduction**

At PRX we take your privacy seriously and will only use your personal information to administer your account and to provide the products and services you have requested from us. PRX is committed to safeguarding the privacy of visitors to our Web site and users of the other services available through our site (the "Service(s)"). We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you provide us remains private and is used only for the purposes set forth herein.

PRX can be found at <https://www.prx.org/company/about#contact>. Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at privacy@prx.org.

This privacy policy details our commitment to protect your information and the limited manner in which we will use that information to provide and improve our provision of the Services.

###  **Important Terms Used Throughout This Privacy Policy**

Throughout this privacy policy we use several specialized terms. "Personally Identifiable Information" (PII) is information that tells us specifically who you are, like your name, street address, email address, billing address, credit card number and expiration date. "User Information" means all Personally Identifiable Information and any other forms of information discussed in this privacy policy, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address of a user's computer. We use the term "aggregate" when we combine information from various persons or users. Information is said to be "anonymized" if it does not identify individual persons or entities or associate a particular person or entity with such information.

###  **Information We Collect and How We Use It**

If you visit our site to browse, we will only collect and store the domain name and host from which a user accessed the Internet (e.g., aol.com), the IP address of the user's computer, the user's browser software and operating system, the date and time the user accesses the site and the Internet address of any Web site from which the user linked directly to our site or to which the user links after visiting our site. PRX also automatically collects information about your interactions with media content on third-party sites that include our Embeddable Player. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to sections of our sites, to determine from where our visitors linked and to where our visitors link from the sites and to help us make our sites more useful. For example, we organize and analyze IP addresses so that we can provide efficient service, enhance security, monitor appropriate usage and produce traffic volume statistics. This type of information is sometimes shared with third parties, such as when we aggregate and disclose site traffic information for marketing purposes. When we share such information with third parties we will require them to abide by the standards of this privacy policy.

If you register or engage in a transaction while at our site, to make full use of our Services you will need to complete our registration process. We collect and store the Personally Identifiable Information you provide through this registration process, including your user ID and password, which we may elect to provide for you. If you engage in a transaction while logged on to our site, then we collect and store information about the transaction. If you send us communications, then we may collect such communications in a file specific to you.

We use the information we collect from you as a registered user to build features that we hope will make the Services more attractive and easier for you to use. This may include better customer support and timely notice of new services. We may share User Information with our partners and affiliates that are committed to serving your need for the Services and improving your user experience, but will require such third parties to abide by the standards of this privacy policy. We may also share aggregate anonymized data relating to activity on the site and use of the Services, such as demographical and statistical information, for marketing, research and other purposes. Furthermore, we may need to disclose User Information to law enforcement or other government officials if appropriate for your protection or in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or our users to legal liability.

We use a Google Analytics feature based on Display Advertising that collects demographic and interest information about our visitors. We use this information to better target sponsor messaging within the products we create. Visitors can easily opt-out of the collection of this information by using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or using the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

###  **If You Do Not Wish to Disclose User Information**

If you do not want to provide us with certain User Information then you may opt out by not using the Service that provides us with such User Information. For example, if you do not want us to retain your name, then you may choose not to become a registered user. You will not be entitled to the benefits of registration, but you are still free to browse the site and to visit the parts of the site accessible to non-registrants.

###  **Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that our site can send to your browser for storage on your hard drive. Cookies can make your use of our site easier by saving your status and preferences upon visits to our site. The cookies are refreshed every time you enter the site. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you may be able to change the settings to refuse cookies or to be alerted when cookies are being sent. We use cookies for two purposes: (1) to enable PRX to customize information for certain segments of its customer base; and (2) in some instances, to associate you with your User Information. For example, through the use of cookies you may log in automatically and thereby save you time. Rejection of cookies will interfere with your ability to log in and use certain interactive Services on the site.

###  **Control of Your Password**

Except as specifically permitted by this privacy policy or your User Agreement you may not disclose your PRX password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your PRX password you may lose control over your Personally Identifiable Information, and you will be responsible for any legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password or, if we provided your password, notify PRX so that we may issue you a new password.

###  **Removal or Correction of Personally Identifiable Information**

You have the right to withdraw consent at any time and may do so by signing in to your Account and clicking the “Deactivate user account” link. We will erase your personal data when you withdraw your consent.

You may also "Unsubscribe" from the site by emailing help@prx.org with the subject "unsubscribe" and your username in the message. We will email you back as soon as your account has been disabled. This will completely erase all your personal information from our systems. If you unsubscribe, you will lose access to the parts of the site for which you must provide such Personally Identifiable Information in order to gain access.

If your Personally Identifiable Information is edited by you, we will not make any attempt to apply your edit to backup copies that we may have of the information, and in the event that it is necessary for us to restore our database from a backup, it is possible that your edit would be lost and the information previous to your edit would be restored. In such an event, we might not be able to determine that this had happened. Your recourse in such a case is to edit the information again.

If you unsubscribe, the Personally Identifiable Information in your user record will not be displayed to users other than administrators. In addition, content or materials you have posted or uploaded to the site will no longer be displayed to users other than administrators, with the exception of certain materials that may be required for proper functioning of the Services (e.g., a piece licensed by a station will be viewable and downloadable by that station for the remaining term of the license). Information, content, and materials may be retained in our database and backup copies thereof, for our records, and as necessary for us to comply with governmental orders, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce any agreement you have entered into through our sites and as otherwise deemed reasonably necessary by us.

###  **Underage Users**

If you are under 16 years of age, do not send us any information about yourself, including your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. If we discover that we have collected any personally identifying information from a child under the age of 16, we will remove that information from our records as soon as possible.

###  **Third Parties**

This privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of User Information collected by PRX. If you disclose information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of such information regardless of their affiliation or relationship with PRX. Because PRX does not control the privacy practices of third parties you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of those third parties. When you link to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that Web site. We encourage you to ask questions and review the applicable privacy policy before you disclose your personal information to third parties.

We do not try to control, and disclaim responsibility for, information provided by other users or third parties that is made available through our site. Such information may contain errors, intentional or otherwise, or may be offensive, inappropriate or inaccurate, and in some cases may be mislabeled or deceptively labeled.

###  **Miscellaneous**

PRX may from time to time change this privacy policy with or without notice, so please check it regularly for any changes or updates. For future reference, PRX will make a link to the current privacy policy available to you on your screen when you are on our Web site. Your use of the site constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and your assent to any modification thereto.

All data subjects under the GDPR have the following rights with respect to their data: rights of access, rectification, erasure, data portability, and right to be forgotten. Data is retained for as long as your account is active. At any time, you may lodge a complaint about our compliance with this policy with a Supervisory Authority.

###  **How do I contact PRX?**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you can [contact us.](https://www.prx.org/company/about#contact)
